Guide to the William David Allred Papers 1969-002
University of Houston Libraries Special Collections
- Political File, 1966-1980
  - Fowler, Mr. Willard (Box 28)
  - Fowler, Mrs. William J. (Box 28)
  - Fox, Estille A. (Box 28)
  - Fox, Gerald G. (Box 28)
  - Fox, Mr. James R. (Box 28)
  - Fairfax County House (Box 28)
  - Famous Writers School (Box 28)
  - Far Eastern Trip (Box 28)
  - Fehnenberger, Mr. & Mrs. Tom (Box 28)
  - Ferguson, Mrs. Maxine (Box 28)
  - Fields, Mr. & Mrs. W. C. Jr. (Box 28)
  - Fihelly, Mr. & Mrs. Art (Box 28)
  - First Christian Church Pearsall, Texas (Box 28)
  - First Christian Church, Knox City (Box 28)
  - First Christian Church of Graham (Box 28)
  - First National Bank of Waco (Box 28)
  - Fisher, Joe J. (Box 28)
  - Forehand, Mr. & Mrs. Arvil D. (Box 28)
  - Foundry Counseling Service (Box 28)
  - Friendly, Mr. & Mrs. Fred W. (Box 28)
  - Furniture Papers (Box 28)
  - Francis, Sam (Box 29)
  - Francisco, Mr. Jack (Box 29)
  - Franklin, Charles (Box 29)
  - Frasier, Vada May (Box 29)
  - Frazier, Mrs. Alma (Box 29)
  - Frederick, Miss Ruth (Box 29)
  - Free Enterprise (Box 29)
  - Freedom Month (Box 29)
  - Freedom of Information (Box 29)
  - Freedom of the Press (Box 29)
  - Freeman, Mr. & Mrs. O. T. (Box 29)
  - Friberg School (Box 29)
  - Fritzler, Mr. & Mrs. W. G. (Box 29)
  - Frnka, Mrs. Carrie (Box 29)
  - Froede, James A. (Box 29)
  - Frost, Tim (Box 29)
  - Frye, Mr. & Mrs. James E. (Box 29)
  - Fuhs, Mrs. Mary Sue (Box 29)
  - Fuller, Mr. & Mrs. Jerry (Box 29)
  - Fuller, Stan (Box 29)
  - Funderburk, Mr. & Mrs. H. N. (Box 29)
  - Funeral Directors (Box 29)
  - Funeral Homes (Box 29)
  - Funland (Box 29)
  - Furrh, Mrs. James W. (Box 29)
  - Fain, John E. (Box 29)
  - Fairclough, Tom (Box 29)
  - Falwell, Jerry (Box 29)
  - Fambrough, Tim D. (Box 29)
  - Family Affairs (Box 29)
  - Family Court Services Dept. (Box 29)
  - Family Law (Box 29)
  - Family Life (Box 29)
  - Family Planning (Box 29)
  - Family Relations (Box 29)
  - Fancher, Carlton (Box 29)
  - Fancher, Mrs. Edith (Box 29)
  - Fanous, Labib (Box 29)
  - Farabee, Joseph H. (Box 29)
  - Farabee, Mr. & Mrs. Joseph R. (Box 29)
  - Farenthold, Emilie (Box 29)
  - Farenthold, Mrs. Frances (Box 29)
  - Farley, Dan (Box 29)
  - Farley, Mrs. Opha (Box 29)
  - Farm Bureau (Box 29)
  - Farmer, Mr. Jack (Box 29)
  - Farmer, Mr. & Mrs. Jim (Box 29)
  - Farm Workers (Box 29)
  - Farris, Charlye O. (Box 29)
  - Farrer, Ms. Edna (Box 29)
  - Farrier, Mrs. F. M. (Box 29)
  - Fatheree, Richard (Box 29)
  - Fayette County (Box 29)
  - Faykus, Ms. Joyce (Box 29)
  - Feather, Mrs. H. M. (Box 29)
  - Featherston, W. B. (Box 29)
  - Featherston, W. S. (Box 29)
  - Featt, Viola (Box 29)
  - Federal Aviation Agency (Box 29)
  - Federal Communications Commission (Box 29)
  - Federal Government (Box 29)
  - Federal Housing Administration (Box 29)
  - Federal Trade Commission (Box 29)
  - Feigelson, Gene (Box 29)
  - Feille, Bill B. (Box 29)
  - Feloglio, Dena (Box 29)
  - Felts, W. J. (Box 29)
  - Feltz, Mrs. Alma (Box 29)
  - Fenner, Mr. & Mrs. James (Box 29)
  - Fenner, Margie (Box 29)
  - Fenoglio, Cecil (Box 29)
  - Fenwick, Mr. & Mrs. James L. (Box 29)
  - Ferguson, Dolphine (Box 29)
  - Ferguson, Mrs. Quata (Box 29)
  - Ferguson, Wilma (Box 29)
  - Fernandez, Mr. & Mrs. Edward J. (Box 29)
  - Ferrier, Nelda (Box 29)
  - Field, Fred B. (Box 29)
  - Fields, Cal (Box 29)
  - Fields, Mrs. Mildred (Box 29)
  - Fields, Vernon Donald (Box 29)
  - Fieldsen, Bonnie (Box 29)
  - Fieldsend, Mr. Larry (Box 29)
  - Fillman, Mrs. Iva (Box 29)
  - Fillmore, Clyde (Box 29)
  - Fillmore, H. W. (Box 29)
  - Finances (Box 29)
  - Financial (Box 29)
  - Financial Institutions Committee (Box 29)
  - Findley, Mr. & Mrs. L. E. (Box 29)
  - Fine Arts (Box 29)
  - Finer, Mrs. Max (Box 29)
  - Finkenbiner, Sgt. Richard L. (Box 29)
  - Finnell, Mr. Les (Box 29)
  - Finney, James (Box 29)
  - Firearms (Box 29)
  - Firefighters (Box 29)
  - Fire Marshall (Box 29)
  - F.I.R.S.T. (Box 29)
  - First Mercantile Corporation (Box 29)
  - First Savings and Loan Association of Burkburnett (Box 29)
  - First Step, Inc. (Box 29)
  - First Wichita National Bank (Box 29)
  - Fischer, Anna L. (Box 29)
  - Fish and Fishing (Box 29)
  - Fish and Wildlife Services (Box 29)
  - Fisher, Billie (Box 29)
  - Fisher, Clarence (Box 29)
  - Fisher, Mr. & Mrs. Paul W. (Box 29)
  - Fite, Mr. & Mrs. Jake (Box 29)
  - Fite, Sue (Box 29)
  - Fitts, Mr. & Mrs. Joe (Box 29)
  - Fitzgerald, Mrs. Dorothy (Box 29)
  - Flack, Al Jr. (Box 29)
  - Flaks, Ms. Lucile (Box 29)
  - Flatt, Crys (Box 29)
  - Fleming, Ms. Claudia (Box 29)
  - Fleming, Ms. Helen H. (Box 29)
  - Fletcher, Mrs. Charles D. (Box 29)
  - Fletcher, Dr. & Mrs. D. E. (Box 29)
  - Flippin, Mrs. Dickie (Box 29)
  - Flood Control (Box 29)
  - Flooding (Box 29)
  - Florence, Buck (Box 29)
  - Flournoy, Mrs. Corliss B. (Box 29)
  - Flowers, Kenneth W. (Box 29)
  - Flowers, Mrs. Lottie Mae (Box 29)
  - Flowers Industries Political Action Committee (Box 29)
  - Floyd, Danny (Box 29)
  - Floyd, Ms. Lahoma (Box 29)
  - Flusche, Gary (Box 29)
  - Foltz, Rev. Clyde D. (Box 29)
  - Fondren, Mr. & Mrs. Pete (Box 29)
  - Forbes, Tom (Box 29)
  - Forcher, Mr. & Mrs. Terry (Box 29)
  - Ford, Mr. Elmer (Larry) (Box 29)
  - Ford, Mary (Box 29)
  - Foreign Affairs (Box 29)
  - Formby, Mrs. Jan (Box 29)
  - Forsythe, Mr. C. E. (Box 29)
  - Fortado, Mrs. Juanita (Box 29)
  - Fortinberry, Mrs. Mozelle (Box 29)
  - Fortner, Rev. Thomas E. (Box 29)
  - Fort Worth St. School (Box 29)
  - Foster, Mrs. Dale (Box 29)
  - Foster Grandparents (Box 29)
  - Foster, Mrs. J. Lewis (Box 29)
  - Foster, Mrs. Peggy (Box 29)
  - Foster, Sharon (Box 29)
  - Foster, Mr. William (Box 29)
  - Fougeron, Mrs. Laverne (Box 29)
  - Fowler, Madeline (Box 29)
  - Fowler, Robert Mike (Box 29)
  - Fox, Ms. Edwena (Box 29)
  - Fox, Mrs. Gina (Box 29)
  - Fox, Mr. & Mrs. Tom C. (Box 29)
  - Francell, Ms. Beth (Box 29)
  - Francis, Ms. Alma (Box 29)
  - Francis, Joe L. (Box 29)
  - Franklin, Linda (Box 29)
  - Frank Phillips College (Box 29)
  - Franks, Betty (Box 29)
  - Franks, Ms. Helen (Box 29)
  - Fratt, Ms. Veola (Box 29)
  - Frazee, Bob (Box 29)
  - Frazier, Mrs. T. J. (Box 29)
  - Fredericksburg, Texas (Box 29)
  - Freman, Mr. C. O. (Box 29)
  - Freeman, Dovey (Box 29)
  - Freeman, Ms. Helen (Box 29)
  - Freeman, Herbert (Box 29)
  - Freemon, Mrs. Eddie (Box 29)
  - Freemon, Mrs. F. A. (Box 29)
  - Freeman, John C. (Box 29)
  - Friedman, Dr. & Mrs. S. H. (Box 29)
  - Fritz, Edward (Box 29)
  - Fry, Bernie & Lorene (Box 29)
  - Fryar, Mrs. Charles W. (Box 29)
  - Fugett, Mr. Joe A. (Box 29)
  - Fuhrmann, Ms. Mary Helen (Box 29)
  - Fuhrman, Ms. Ruth (Box 29)
  - Fulbright, Mr. W. C. (Box 29)
  - Fulfer, Judy (Box 29)
  - Fuller, Mrs. Tommy (Box 29)
  - Fulmer, Mrs. Charles (Box 29)
  - Funderbirk, Elizabeth (Box 29)
  - Funk, Dr. Martin A. (Box 29)
  - Funston, Keith (Box 29)
  - Funston, Randy (Box 29)
  - Furiston, Ms. Estelle (Box 29)
  - Furr, Bedford (Box 29)
  - Fagg, Larry Dyke (Box 30)
  - Faith City Mission (Box 30)
  - Falfurrias, Texas (Box 30)
  - Fan Coach, Inc. (Box 30)
  - Fannin, Marvin (Box 30)
  - Rusty Farabee (Box 30)
  - Farenthold, Mr. & Mrs. Dudley Tarlton (Box 30)
  - Faris, Randall K. (Box 30)
  - Faris, Wynn (Box 30)
  - Farmer, E. H. (Box 30)
  - Farmer, Mrs. J. B. (Box 30)
  - Farr, Mrs. J. Norman (Box 30)
  - Farrell, Howard (Box 30)
  - Farrell, Mr. & Mrs. W. N. (Box 30)
  - Farris, Mrs. Roberta (Box 30)
  - Faulk, Ms. Dorothy (Box 30)
  - Faulkenberry, Ms. Ruby (Box 30)
  - Faye, Esta (Box 30)
  - Faye, Gilbert (Box 30)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box 30)
  - Federal Land Bank (Box 30)
  - Federation of North Texas Area Universities (Box 30)
  - Feille, Mr. & Mrs. Bryan (Box 30)
  - Feliz, Joe (Box 30)
  - Felty, Mr. & Mrs. F. T. (Box 30)
  - Felty, F. T. Jr. (Box 30)
  - Fenoglio, Tony (Box 30)
  - Fenn, Mr. J. R. III (Box 30)
  - Fenner, Mrs. W. L. (Box 30)
  - Ferguson, Eileen A. (Box 30)
  - Ferguson, Floyd S. (Box 30)
  - Ferguson, Vicki (Box 30)
  - Ferrell, Ms. Marion (Box 30)
  - FFA (Box 30)
  - Fideli, Joe (Box 30)
  - Fields, Johnny (Box 30)
  - Finance Commission of Texas (Box 30)
  - Financial Affairs (Box 30)
  - Financial Disclosure (Box 30)
  - Finney, Dr. Louis A. (Box 30)
  - Fire Ants (Box 30)
  - Fire Extinguishers (Box 30)
  - Firemen (Box 30)
  - Fireworks (Box 30)
  - First national Bank San Antonio, TX. (Box 30)
  - First State Bank of Uvalde (Box 30)
  - First United Methodist Church (Box 30)
  - First-Wichita National Bank (Box 30)
  - Fish (Box 30)
  - Fisher, Ethel (Box 30)
  - Fisher, Major Don R. (Box 30)
  - Fisher, Rev. Harry W. (Box 30)
  - Fisher, Wayne (Box 30)
  - Fishing (Box 30)
  - Fitzgerald, Willie L. (Box 30)
  - Fleming, Mrs. Nova (Box 30)
  - Flick, Alta M. (Box 30)
  - Flink, Charles (Box 30)
  - Flippin, Dan (Box 30)
  - Florida (Box 30)
  - Flouridation (Box 30)
  - Flournoy, Dr. Dick (Box 30)
  - Flowers, Charles H. (Box 30)
  - Flowers, Mrs. Jane (Box 30)
  - Floyd, Mr. & Mrs. Guy (Box 30)
  - Flynn, Mr. & Mrs. William T. (Box 30)
  - Foley, Bernice (Box 30)
  - Foley, Bob (Box 30)
  - Food (Box 30)
  - Food & Drug Administration (Box 30)
  - Food Stamps (Box 30)
  - Forcher, Randle D. (Box 30)
  - Ford, Mr. & Mrs. Claude H. (Box 30)
  - Ford, Clifford E. (Box 30)
  - Fore, Maude Williams (Box 30)
  - Foreman, Mr. & Mrs. Wilson (Box 30)
  - Forestry (Box 30)
  - Foreign Policy Association (Box 30)
  - Former Texas Rangers Association (Box 30)
  - Fort Bend County, Texas (Box 30)
  - Fort Hood, Texas (Box 30)
  - Fort Worth & Denver Railway Co. (Box 30)
  - Fort Worth, Texas (Box 30)
  - Foster, James D. (Box 30)
  - Foster, Mr. & Mrs. L. J. (Box 30)
  - Foster, Mrs. Sharon (Box 30)
  - Foulis, Stella (Box 30)
  - Four-H (Box 30)
  - Four Winds Industrial Foundation Inc. (Box 30)
  - Four Winds RC & D (Box 30)
  - Fowler, Mr. & Mrs. Ben T. (Box 30)
  - Fowler Home (Box 30)
  - Fowler, Mr. & Mrs. John M. (Box 30)
  - Fox, Leeroy (Box 30)
  - Fox, Milton E. (Box 30)
  - Foyce, James B. (Box 30)
  - Foyt, Mr. Anton (Box 30)
  - Francell, Mr. Larry (Box 30)
  - Francis, Cordelia (Box 30)
  - Francis, Maj. C. (Box 30)
  - Francis, Doris (Box 30)
  - Francis, Madge (Box 30)
  - Francis, Mr. S. C. (Box 30)
  - Frandolig, Mr. & Mrs. Charles (Box 30)
  - Frank, Mr. Bob (Box 30)
  - Frank, Ms. Sally (Box 30)
  - Franklin, Dale (Box 30)
  - Fraser, Dorothy (Box 30)
  - Frazee, Robert G. (Box 30)
  - Freeman, Mrs. Anna (Box 30)
  - Freeman, Mrs. Annie (Box 30)
  - Freeman, Mr. John C. (Box 30)
  - Freeman, Ms. June (Box 30)
  - Freeman, Mr. & Mrs. Orren (Box 30)
  - Freeman, Richard (Box 30)
  - Freeman, Ronnie (Box 30)
  - Free the Slow, Inc. (Box 30)
  - Friberg, J. Walter (Box 30)
  - Friend, E. M. (Box 30)
  - Friend, Dr. Llerna B. (Box 30)
  - Friends of the Earth (Box 30)
  - Frierson (Box 30)
  - Fritsche, R. C. (Box 30)
  - Froehner, George W. (Box 30)
  - Froman, Bill (Box 30)
  - Fuhrmann, Maria (Box 30)
  - Fuhrmann, Mr. & Mrs. V. L. (Box 30)
  - Fulfer, Carolyn (Box 30)
  - Full Gospel Businessmen's Fellowship, Inc. (Box 30)
  - Fuller, Ellen (Box 30)
  - Fullerton, Dr. H. M. (Box 30)
  - Funston, G. Dean (Box 30)
  - Funston, Mrs. Turner (Box 30)
  - Furman, Don G. (Box 30)
  - Furniture (Box 30)
  - Gage (Box 30)
  - Gallagher, Michael D. (Box 30)
  - Gaines, Mr. & Mrs. R. E. (Box 30)
  - Gaines, Sydney A. (Box 30)
  - Gainesville, Texas (Box 30)
  - Galligar, Sharon (Box 30)
  - Galloup, Furl (Box 30)
  - Galloway, Mr. Joe L. (Box 30)
  - Galvan, Ms. Juanita (Box 30)
  - Galveston (Box 30)
  - Galvez, Mr & Mrs. Primo (Box 30)
  - Gambling (Box 30)
  - Gammage, Robert (Box 30)
  - Gann, Laura (Box 30)
  - Gannon, Mr. & Mrs. John V. (Box 30)
  - Gantt, Mr. Joe (Box 30)
  - Garages (Box 30)
  - Garcia, Guillermo (Box 30)
  - Garcia, J. A. Jr. (Box 30)
  - Garcia, Jesse (Box 30)
  - Garcia, Matt (Box 30)
  - Garcia, Simon (Box 30)
  - Gardner, Ms. Darlene (Box 30)
  - Gardner, Mrs. Flora (Box 30)
  - Gardner, G. G. (Box 30)
  - Gardner, Thelma (Box 30)
  - Garland, Mr. & Mrs. Gad (Box 30)
  - Garner, Mike (Box 30)
  - Garner, Roy E. (Box 30)
  - Garnishment (Box 30)
  - Garrett, James M. (Box 30)
  - Garrett, Joi Anne (Box 30)
  - Garrett, Kenneth G. (Box 30)
  - Garrison, Col. Homer (Box 30)
  - Garst, Samuel S. (Box 30)
  - Garvin, Connie (Box 30)
  - Gary Job Corps Center (Box 30)
  - Gas (Box 30)
  - Gaskin, Miss. Zela (Box 30)
  - Gasparek, Danny (Box 30)
  - Gaston, Frank (Box 30)
  - Gatlin, R. E. (Box 30)
  - Gaudry, Margaret (Box 30)
  - Gauerholz, Mr. & Mrs. Larry (Box 30)
  - Gay, Genevieve (Box 30)
  - Gay, Mr. & Mrs. John W. (Box 30)
  - Gay Liberation (Box 30)
  - Gehring, Mrs. Oscar M. (Box 30)
  - Geiger, Richard S. (Box 30)
  - Geis, Diane (Box 30)
  - Gellman, Tobi Kay (Box 30)
  - General Land Office (Box 30)
  - General Telephone Co. (Box 30)
  - Gentry, Jack (Box 30)
  - Gentry, Jim (Box 30)
  - Geology (Box 30)
  - George, Dennis (Box 30)
  - George, Mrs. Kay (Box 30)
  - Germany, John L. (Box 30)
  - Gesham, Clark (Box 30)
  - Gettys, Carl R. (Box 30)
  - Geyer, Dr. C. Mac (Box 30)
  - Gibbons, John L. (Box 30)
  - Gibbs, Edgar L.
  - Gibson, Barbara (Box 30)
  - Gibson, Frank (Box 30)
  - Gibson, George F. (Box 30)
  - Gibson, Jerry (Box 30)
  - Gibson, Mark (Box 30)
  - Gibson, Mr. & Mrs. Richard (Box 30)
  - Gibson, Sherree (Box 30)
  - Gifted Children (Box 30)
  - Galloway, Mrs. Ottis (Box 31)
  - Gambill, Rupert (Box 31)
  - Gamble, Mrs. Robert L. (Box 31)
  - Gard, Miss Dorris (Box 31)
  - Gard, Mrs. Ruth (Box 31)
  - Garden Clubs (Box 31)
  - Gardner, G. G. (Box 31)
  - Gardner, Jess (Box 31)
  - Garland, Texas (Box 31)
  - Garner, Roy E. (Box 31)
  - Garrett, Mrs. Alvin (Box 31)
  - Garrett, Mrs. Dorothy (Box 31)
  - Garrison, Col. Homer (Box 31)
  - Garrison, James R. (Box 31)
  - Garrison, Miss Juanita (Box 31)
  - Garrett, George (Box 31)
  - Gaston, Lois (Box 31)
  - Gates, Mr. & MRs. James A. (Box 31)
  - Gatesville School for Boys (Box 31)
  - Gavin, John J. (Box 31)
  - Gavin, Robert (Box 31)
  - Gay, Mrs. Christine (Box 31)
  - Gaynor, G. A. (Box 31)
  - Gee, Mrs. Movelda (Box 31)
  - General Land Office (Box 31)
  - Gengelbach, Mr. James G. (Box 31)
  - Gentry, Mr. G. C. (Box 31)
  - Gentry, Jack (Box 31)
  - Genung, Mr. & Mrs. Paul (Box 31)
  - George, Mr. Dennis (Box 31)
  - George, Mrs. J. F. (Box 31)
  - Gerhard & Schulle Junior (Box 31)
  - Gibbens, Wayne (Box 31)
  - Gibbs, Miss Sue (Box 31)
  - Gibson, Mrs. Barney (Box 31)
  - Gibson, Larry (Box 31)
  - Gibson, Ms. Mattie L. (Box 31)
  - Gibson, Mr. & Mrs. Richard (Box 31)
  - Gibson, Miss Stella (Box 31)
  - Gilbreath, Mrs. Alice (Box 31)
  - Gilbreath, Ray (Box 31)
  - Gilbreth, Mr. Tray (Box 31)
  - Giles Grady Co., Realtors (Box 31)
  - Giles, Mrs. L. D. (Box 31)
  - Gilkerson, Morris A. (Box 31)
  - Gill, Bob (Box 31)
  - Gill, Mrs. Marie (Box 31)
  - Gillam, Vernon B. (Box 31)
  - Gilleland, Mrs. Ora E. (Box 31)
  - Gillispie, Mrs. Marjorie (Box 31)
  - Ginnings, J. I. (Box 31)
  - Girl Scouts (Box 31)
  - Givens, Cecil H. (Box 31)
  - Gladden, Don (Box 31)
  - Glandon, Miss Peggy (Box 31)
  - Glenn, Mr. James Michael (Box 31)
  - Glidewell, Dr. Allen (Box 31)
  - Glosup, Miss Paula (Box 31)
  - Glover, Mr. Bill (Box 31)
  - Glover, Mr. Joe (Box 31)
  - Gloyna, Earnest F. (Box 31)
  - Godbey, Mrs. Ruth Horner (Box 31)
  - Goddard, Col. Mary A. (Box 31)
  - Goettman, Mrs. Eugene (Box 31)
  - Goforth, Mr. Leon (Box 31)
  - Goforth, Mr. O. B. (Box 31)
  - Goldblatt, Mr. Max (Box 31)
  - Golus, Felix P. (Box 31)
  - Gonzalez, Henry B. (Box 31)
  - Goodwin, Mrs. Katherine (Box 31)
  - Goodwin, Mr. W. J. (Box 31)
  - Gordon, Mrs. W. T. (Box 31)
  - Goree, Sarah D. (Box 31)
  - Gose, S. M. (Box 31)
  - Gose, Steve (Box 31)
  - Gowan, William (Box 31)
  - Gower, Charles R. (Box 31)
  - Goulding, W. L. (Box 31)
  - Gouldy, Roland (Box 31)
  - Governor's Commission on the Status of Women (Box 31)
  - Governor's Committee on Aging (Box 31)
  - Governor's Committee on Public School Education (Box 31)
  - Governor's Mansion (Box 31)
  - Gowan, Larry Warren (Box 31)
  - Gowdy, Joe C. (Box 31)
  - Grace, Bill (Box 31)
  - Grace, Henry (Box 31)
  - Grace, Phillip M. (Box 31)
  - Graff, Mr. E. E. (Box 31)
  - Gragg, Robert (Box 31)
  - Graham, George (Box 31)
  - Graham, Mr. & Mrs. H. M. (Box 31)
  - Grain Sorghum Producers Association (Box 31)
  - Grantham, Mrs. Allen (Box 31)
  - Grantom, Mrs. Robert (Box 31)
  - Grauerholz, Mr. & Mrs. Larry (Box 31)
  - Graves, Hon. Curtis (Box 31)
  - Graves, Miss Joan (Box 31)
  - Gray, Brent (Box 31)
  - Gray, Harry L. (Box 31)
  - Gray, J. D. (Box 31)
  - Gray, Mr. Lewis A. (Box 31)
  - Gray, Noble (Box 31)
  - Gray, Mr. & Mrs. W. J. (Box 31)
  - Great Western Finance Co. (Box 31)
  - Green, Mrs. Barbara (Box 31)
  - Green, Mr. & Mrs. Billy M. (Box 31)
  - Green, Charles Leroy (Box 31)
  - Green, Mrs. Louise (Box 31)
  - Green, Roy E. (Box 31)
  - Greenway, Mr. John W. (Box 31)
  - Greenway, Ruth (Box 31)
  - Greenwood, Jim (Box 31)
  - Greenwood, Mr. S. B. (Box 31)
  - Greer, Dewitt C. (Box 31)
  - Greer, Mr. H. C. (Box 31)
  - Gresham, G. C. (Box 31)
  - Gridiron (Box 31)
  - Grieder, Mrs. Berniece Martin (Box 31)
  - Griffis, Mrs. F. M. (Box 31)
  - Griffitts, Mr. & Mrs. Loyd (Box 31)
  - Grote, Wilbert L. (Box 31)
  - Grover, Henry C. (Box 31)
  - Groves, Glenn (Box 31)
  - Grubbs, Jack (Box 31)
  - Grusendorf, Dr. A. A. (Box 31)
  - Guadalupe Mountains National Park (Box 31)
  - Gues, Mr. & Mrs. Weldon S. Jr. (Box 31)
  - Guffin, Mrs. Orea (Box 31)
  - Guidroz, Revamae (Box 31)
  - Guinn, Mrs. Al (Box 31)
  - Gun Legislation (Box 31)
  - Gun Regulation (Box 31)
  - Guthrie, Mr. N. E. Jr. (Box 31)
  - Guynes, Jack (Box 31)
  - Gwinn, Mr. Delton B. (Box 31)
  - Gabbert, Mrs. Linda (Box 32)
  - Gage, Hardy (Box 32)
  - Gaines, Craig T. (Box 32)
  - Gainesville State School (Box 32)
  - Gainesville, Texas (Box 32)
  - Gallegos, Fred (Box 32)
  - Galligar, Mr. Charles (Box 32)
  - Galloway, Harvey (Box 32)
  - Galloway, Ms. Patricia (Box 32)
  - Galloway, William (Box 32)
  - Galveston, Texas (Box 32)
  - Galveston College (Box 32)
  - Gamble, Mrs. Cathy (Box 32)
  - Gamble, Jerry (Box 32)
  - Gambling (Box 32)
  - Gamboa, Mr. B. (Box 32)
  - Gambrell, Mrs. Arthur L. (Box 32)
  - Gammage, Bob (Box 32)
  - Gandy, Ms. Micheal G. (Box 32)
  - Gann, Mrs. W. A. (Box 32)
  - Garcia, Gilbert (Box 32)
  - Garcia, Matt (Box 32)
  - Garcia, Tony (Box 32)
  - Gard, Ms. Dianne (Box 32)
  - Garden Club (Box 32)
  - Gardner, Ms. Darlene (Box 32)
  - Garland, Gad (Box 32)
  - Garnier, Ms. D. (Box 32)
  - Garrett, Mr. & Mrs. Charles (Box 32)
  - Garrett, Ms. Effie (Box 32)
  - Garrett, Jim (Box 32)
  - Garrett, Joi Anne (Box 32)
  - Garrett, Martha (Box 32)
  - Garrison, Ms. Bettye (Box 32)
  - Garrison, Ms. Kaye (Box 32)
  - Garnett, Ed (Box 32)
  - Gartung, Frank (Box 32)
  - Garvin, Thomas C. (Box 32)
  - Garwood, Will (Box 32)
  - Gary, Jess (Box 32)
  - Gas (Box 32)
  - Gasohol (Box 32)
  - Gaskill, Lonnie (Box 32)
  - Gaston, Frank (Box 32)
  - Gates, Ms. Jean R. (Box 32)
  - Gateway Inn (Box 32)
  - Gaudry, Ms. Margaret (Box 32)
  - Gee, Mrs. Earl (Box 32)
  - Gee, Mr. & Mrs. Harold W. (Box 32)
  - Geiger, Mr. Bruce (Box 32)
  - Geiger, Lois (Box 32)
  - Geiger, Richard (Box 32)
  - Geis, Mrs. Kathryn (Box 32)
  - Geistweidt, Gerald (Box 32)
  - Geisler, Marvin (Box 32)
  - General Cinema (Box 32)
  - General Motors Corporation (Box 32)
  - Gentry, Jim (Box 32)
  - Geology (Box 32)
  - George, Mrs. Richard M. (Box 32)
  - George, Mrs. Taylor (Box 32)
  - George, Wanda (Box 32)
  - Georgia-Pacific Corporation (Box 32)
  - Gettys, Carl R. (Box 32)
  - Geyman, Mr. & Mrs. L. L. (Box 32)
  - Gibbins, Bob (Box 32)
  - Gibbs, Mr. & Mrs. John P. (Box 32)
  - Gibbs, W. B. (Box 32)
  - Gibson, Charles (Box 32)
  - Gibson, Jay (Box 32)
  - Gibson, J. R. (Box 32)
  - Gibson, J. W. (Box 32)
  - Gibson, John (Box 32)
  - Gibson, Lucille T. (Box 32)
  - Gibson, Mike (Box 32)
  - Gibson, Vikki (Box 32)
  - Gibson, Mrs. W. R. (Box 32)
  - Gideon, Mrs. B. E. (Box 32)
  - Giffin, Mrs. D. A. (Box 32)
  - GI Forum (Box 32)
  - Gifted Children (Box 32)
  - Gilbert, Gary (Box 32)
  - Gilbert, Mrs. Gladys (Box 32)
  - Gilbert, Raymond L. (Box 32)
  - Gilbow, Mrs. Pamela (Box 32)
  - Gilbreath, Mr. Zearl (Box 32)
  - Gilchrist, Ms. Virginia (Box 32)
  - Gilleland, Mr. & Mrs. James (Box 32)
  - Gillespie, Joe R. (Box 32)
  - Gilley, Lanny (Box 32)
  - Gilligan, Ms. Lillie (Box 32)
  - Gilmer, Mr. & Mrs. Claud H. (Box 32)
  - Gilmer, Morgan S. (Box 32)
  - Gipson, Frederick Paul (Box 32)
  - Girlstown, U. S. A. (Box 32)
  - Givens, Ms. Mona (Box 32)
  - Gleghorn, Mrs. Elsie (Box 32)
  - Glenn, Ronald J. (Box 32)
  - Glickman, Mrs. Barbara (Box 32)
  - Glickman, Mr. & Mrs. Barney (Box 32)
  - Glidewell, Mrs. L. P. (Box 32)
  - Glossbrenner, Ernestine V. (Box 32)
  - Glowacki, Ms. Tess (Box 32)
  - Goerig, Mrs. Sue (Box 32)
  - Goerte, Al (Box 32)
  - Goff, Larry D. (Box 32)
  - Gold Cross (Box 32)
  - Golden, Mr. & Mrs. C. C. (Box 32)
  - Golden, Jack (Box 32)
  - Goldston, Ms. Sandra K. (Box 32)
  - Gombeski, Mr. W. R. (Box 32)
  - Gonzales, Arnold (Box 32)
  - Gonzales, Cruz & Gonzalo (Box 32)
  - Gonzales, Mr. & Mrs. Frank F. Jr. (Box 32)
  - Gonzales, Mrs. Juanita (Box 32)
  - Gonzales, Ms. Peggy (Box 32)
  - Gonzalez, Raquel (Box 32)
  - Gooch, Ms. Shirley (Box 32)
  - Goode, Ms. Helen K. (Box 32)
  - Goodloe, Ms. Pearl (Box 32)
  - Goode, Roy L. (Box 32)
  - Goolsby, Ms. Linda (Box 32)
  - Gordon, Mrs. F. R. (Box 32)
  - Gordon, Mr. & Mrs. Robert (Box 32)
  - Gordon, Miss Suzanne (Box 32)
  - Gore, Robert (Box 32)
  - Gorham, Ms. Billie (Box 32)
  - Gormdey, Mrs. Barbara (Box 32)
  - Gose, Tad (Box 32)
  - Gossom, David (Box 32)
  - Gotham, Jeffrey (Box 32)
  - Gould Sisters (Box 32)
  - Government Efficiency (Box 32)
  - Government (Box 32)
  - Governor (Box 32)
  - Governor's Commission of Physical Fitness (Box 32)
  - Governor's Coordinating Office for Visually Handicapped (Box 32)
  - Governor's Energy Advisory Council (Box 32)
  - Governor's Office of Traffic Safety (Box 32)
  - Governor's Office for Volunteer Services (Box 32)
  - Gowan, Mrs. Bill E. (Box 32)
  - Gower, Thomas (Box 32)
  - Graham, Don (Box 32)
  - Graham, James M. (Box 32)
  - Graham, Joseph (Box 32)
  - Graham, Miss Melissa J. (Box 32)
  - Graham, Miles (Box 32)
  - Graham, Sandy (Box 32)
  - Granberry, Wilbur (Box 32)
  - Grant, Ben Z. (Box 32)
  - Grant, Frank A. (Box 32)
  - Grantham, Mr. L. E. (Box 32)
  - Grantom, Ralph (Box 32)
  - Graves, Cecil V. (Box 32)
  - Gray, Mrs. Bert (Box 32)
  - Gray, Price (Box 32)
  - Greater South Texas Cultural Basin (Box 32)
  - Green, Mrs. Elmer (Box 32)
  - Green, Evelyn (Box 32)
  - Green, Rep. Gene (Box 32)
  - Green, George (Box 32)
  - Green, Johnnie (Box 32)
  - Green, Ms. Loraine (Box 32)
  - Green, Sondra (Box 32)
  - Green, Steve (Box 32)
  - Green, Mr. & Mrs. Wilford (Box 32)
  - Greene, Liz (Box 32)
  - Greeno, W. L. (Box 32)
  - Greenroy, Mrs. Joe A. (Box 32)
  - Greenwood, Arch (Box 32)
  - Greer, Flavis (Box 32)
  - Gregg, Mr. C. E. (Box 32)
  - Gregg, James R. (Box 32)
  - Gregg, Ms. Juanita (Box 32)
  - Gresham, Mr. & Mrs. Clark (Box 32)
  - Gresham, Jay (Box 32)
  - Griffin, Jerry (Box 32)
  - Griffin, Mr. John E. (Box 32)
  - Griffin, Mrs. P. (Box 32)
  - Griffin, W. A. (Box 32)
  - Griffith, Mr. Dan (Box 32)
  - Griffith, Gordon (Box 32)
  - Griffitts, O. R. (Box 32)
  - Grimes County (Box 32)
  - Griner, John (Box 32)
  - Grisham, Mr. & Mrs. Charles (Box 32)
  - Groenwold, M. D. (Box 32)
  - Groves, Mr. & Mrs. Donald B. (Box 32)
  - Grubbs, Rep. Walter (Box 32)
  - Gruca, Mary Jo (Box 32)
  - Grundy, Mr. & Mrs. George (Box 32)
  - Guerrero, Ms. Cruzita (Box 32)
  - Guerrero, Mrs. Omzita (Box 32)
  - Groenwold, H. D. & Venice (Box 32)
  - Guidance (Box 32)